acekaraoke.com 2017-09-24

# 

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

We at AceKaraoke.com respect your privacy.  Please review our privacy policy for full details on how your personal information is handled.  By placing an order with us, you have agreed to our privacy policy listed below.

## Information Sharing and Collecting:

AceKaraoke.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  1. 1) We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with AceKaraoke under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help AceKaraoke communicate with you about offers from AceKaraoke. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

  2. 2) We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

  3. 3) We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of AceKaraoke's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

  4. 4) We transfer information about you if AceKaraoke is acquired by or merged with another company.  In this event, AceKaraoke will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Confidentiality and Security:

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

## General:

We reserve the right to send you newsletters regarding AceKaraoke special deals, news and offers through your email address. You will also have the right to unsubscribe to our newsletters.

* * *

## Cookies Policy

Ace Karaoke Corp ("us", "we", or "our") uses cookies on AceKaraoke.com (the "Web Store"). By using the Web Store, you consent to the use of cookies.

Our Cookies Policy explains what cookies are, how we use cookies, how third-parties we may partner with may use cookies on the Web Store, your choices regarding cookies and further information about cookies.

### What are cookies

Cookies are small pieces of text sent by your web browser by a website you visit. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows the Web Store or a third-party to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the Web Store more useful to you. These cookies can also be used to identify you to show you advertisements or send you emails.

Cookies can be "persistent" or "session" cookies.

### How Ace Karaoke Corp uses cookies

When you use and access the Web Store, we may place a number of cookies files in your web browser. 

We use cookies for the following purposes: to enable certain functions of the Web Store, to provide analytics, to store your preferences, to enable advertisements delivery, including behavioral and targeted advertising through 3rd parties. Data collected by cookies include IP address, device type, browser type, time, duration of visit, pages and items that were viewed, location, and more. To learn more about cookies, please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>.

We use both session and persistent cookies on the Web Store and we use different types of cookies to run the Web Store:

\- Essential cookies. We may use essential cookies to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent use of user accounts.

### Third-Party Cookies

In addition to our own cookies, we may also use various third-parties cookies to report usage statistics of the Web Store, deliver advertisements on and through the Web Store, internet advertising networks, and so on.

### What are your choices regarding cookies

If you'd like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.

Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.

### Where can your find more information about cookies

You can learn more about cookies and the following third-party websites:

  * AllAboutCookies: <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>
  * Network Advertising Initiative: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>
